♪The night wind shakes off
the withered leaves♪
♪I open the window and gaze at the moon♪
♪Haze spreads across the river,
lanterns drifting♪
♪I hear the memories rustling♪
♪Garden flowers shed petals one by one♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
swaying with melancholy♪
♪I sigh by the lamp over the long night♪
♪Past memories unfold scene by scene♪
♪It's all your face♪
♪Boldly trampling over my heart♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for love miswritten♪
♪And another for youth passed♪
♪With endless sorrow,
I once traced your silhouette♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for joy and sorrow♪
♪And another for parting and reunion♪
♪I write until splendor fades,
and I am no more♪
=Prelude of the White Snake=
=Episode 14=
Let's go check it out there.
There are some human hunters.
- Yes.
- They're hunting now.
- I can smell it from here.
- Come on, let's look.
Human hunters?
Stop!
This aura feels like a high demon.
Yes.
Let me handle this.
This is my personal human pet.
How dare you lay a hand on him?
What a pity. So this human
belongs to a high demon.
We can't touch him.
Even if it's a high demon,
keeping such a dangerous human
is still wrong.
What if he escapes and hurts us one day?
Useless trash!
You can't even handle
a few human hunters?
You almost ruined my mood.
Now get out of here.
(Myriad Demons House)
Master.
Have all the notices been posted?
They've all been posted, Master.
Someone even tore one down.
They've taken the bait.
You're demons?
Well, we have Leifeng Pagoda.
I let out some
of the demonic aura to cover us.
That makes sense, right?
It does.
The mural holds a world
where humans and demons are swapped.
Humans are evil, and demons are good.
This is absurd.
Why do you think Changming
trapped us inside the mural?
Is it his lair or something?
And he's taking us all down?
Anyway,
saving Aunt comes first.
When I came in,
I saw this notice
at the Myriad Demons House's door.
(Notice)
I heard some lesser demons say
the master of the house
has taken a mortal
who's deeply blessed.
He'll kill her on the right day
as a tribute to heaven.
The master is Changming?
I don't care what "ming" he is.
You know what?
I'm itching for a fight today.
I've been wanting to get him.
But we know too little right now.
I have an idea.
Why don't we split up?
We can each gather intel
and decide later.
- I'll go with Suzhen.
- Sure. I'll go with Qing.
Maybe I should go
with Young Master Xu instead.
Perfect. We'll go together.
Fahai,
give me some of the demonic aura.
Alright, sure.
Just hold onto this.
Is it really that easy?
My lord, everything is prepared.
Well done.
But I need to borrow your body.
Everything I have belongs to you.
Please, my lord, use it as you wish.
I made some inquiries.
The house's bottom two floors
are the dungeon.
But I suspect this might be a trap
set by Changming.
So we'd better confirm
if Aunt is really being held there.
I overheard the demons saying
the master is selecting new women
to perform in the house tonight.
Maybe I should sneak in with them.
No way.
You have no spiritual power at all.
You're only slightly stronger.
You can't go. It's too dangerous.
Thank you for the compliment.
But for Aunt's sake, I have to go.
Suzhen, it's not safe
for you to go alone.
I'll sneak in with you.
Qing,
thank you for helping rescue my aunt.
Then we'll wait for you outside.
Once you've confirmed,
signal us with the bells.
Keep yourself safe.
Suzhen, what's with you today?
You've been looking troubled.
I don't know why,
but I have a feeling that Changming
is targeting me this time.
That's impossible.
If that were true, why would he
take Xu Xian's aunt?
It's just a gut feeling.
You're overthinking it.
You weren't the one who attacked him.
(Myriad Demons House)
Behave yourselves.
Now that you're in the house,
wander off and you're dead.
Take them away.
Move!
Changming would never
let us find Aunt so easily.
Maybe because she's a human,
she's being held in a special place.
It's Aunt's earring.
Aunt?
Aunt.
Are you alright?
The door is made
of demon-suppressing stone.
Don't act rashly.
Why did you come? Leave now.
Aunt, just hold on a little longer.
I'll get Xu Xian in here.
You must be careful.
Don't do anything reckless.
I'm fine.
What's going on?
There's the signal.
Aunt is indeed in there.
Let's go.
The trap is set.
Allow me to give you all
another grand gift.
Enjoy it.
Everyone, follow me!
- Yes, Master!
We can't open this door.
Stand back.
- Are you alright, Aunt?
- I'm fine.
We're getting you out.
Let's go.
Why would they lock her in a cage
made of demon-suppressing stone?
Probably to keep
the demons outside away.
Aunt, are you injured anywhere?
I'm fine.
Are any of you hurt?
Stop chatting already.
We need to move now.
They'll find the dungeon
broken into soon.
We have to leave before they come.
Hurry.
Seize them.
Suzhen, Qing, protect Aunt.
Fahai and I will clear a path.
Hold on. You stay here
and protect Suzhen and Aunt.
With his so-so skills,
I'd better do it.
♪I also gave my youth to someone♪
♪I must admit, you made the journey♪
♪When loving you
became instinct, what's left♪
♪Seals a fate too brutal to amend♪
♪Clumsy and new, we gave our first kiss♪
♪Never thought passionate eyes
would turn cold♪
♪I thought of pulling away,
but I'd barely begun♪
♪Having loved you so deep,
how could I love another♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I'm stubborn,
I never stopped you from loving others♪
♪I shouldn't have been so foolish
to think there was still hope♪
♪But you won't even admit what we had♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I have questions,
I never questioned you♪
♪I'll lock you away and set myself free♪
♪After all, I'm the one you deny♪
♪Having ever loved♪